and what flags do you have on your
а что у тебя за флаги на
T-shirt Yes I even have an American
майке Да у меня даже американский есть
flag there is no T-shirt here What
флаг здесь нету пото я майки Что за
flags Yes I ordered from America on
флаги Да я в Я заказывал с Америки на
Magi on the T-shirt What flags are there Yes this is
маги на майке Что за флаги есть да это
South Park m Yes this is South
Южный парк м да это Южный
Park flags of which countries  Yes,
парк флаги каких стран Да никаких это
none at all, this is South Park What is
вообще никаких это Южный парк Что такое
South Park cartoon
Южный парк мультик
really understood this is
правда понял это
a cartoon
мультик
Hello Good evening where are you
Здравствуйте Добрый вечер вы
from in Russia I can see from your face
откуда в Россия я вижу по лицу город
what kind of city is a thief understood and how do you communicate
какой крада понял а чём общаетесь
Krasnodar resident Well, the only thing is we don't
краснодарец Ну единственное не
swear
ругаемся
understood how you could grow such a hairy chest I
понял как смогли такую грудь волосатую
apologize Me too  I don't want it I just have
извиняюсь Я тоже хочу не у меня просто у
less Well let's sing who's
меня меньше Ну давай поме поем у кого
cooler I just also want to grow
круче Я просто тоже хочу типа отрастить
hair like that Get it just you know girls that's
волос Получи просто знаешь девчонки та
such a testosterone machine for just
такой тестостерон машина за просто
something damn sat Now I was talking talking
что-то блин сидел Сейчас общался общался
talking I think
общался я думаю
okay in short Okay
ладно короче Ладно
sorry
извиняюсь
Well there is  ask questions I will answer Do
Ну есть вопросы задавайте я отвечу А у
you also have vegetation on your back
тебя на на спине тоже
Honestly I don't know maybe
растительность Честно не знаю наверно
there is Can you show me I will show I am
есть А можешь показать я покажу мне
just curious  I have it on my back
интересно просто у меня есть на спине
I wonder if others have it the same or not
Интересно у других так же или не так
Damn I won't lie Well no there isn't Show me Yes
блин Врать не буду Ну не нету Покажи Да
there isn't well turn around normally I don't see
нету ну повернись нормально Я не вижу
Turn your back to the camera
Повернись камере спиной
fly well it can't be that it wasn't there at all
муха ну вот не может быть что вообще не
Sit normally with your back I only see yours
было Сядь нормально спиной Я я вижу твою
Yes  I can't sit down Nor Turn around
только Да не могу я сесть Нор Развернись
Just stand up stand up Turn your back
Просто встань встань Развернись спиной
to
ко
me like that I'll just take off my shirt damn Take off your shirt
мне так я только майку блин Сними майку
I don't
Я же не
see you're starting to ask for
вижу начинаешь уже просить
too much yeah Now okay let's do it for fun
много да Сейчас ладно давай ради прикола
or what I'm not interested Look I
или что не мне интересно Смотри у меня
have some hair here and I have hair in the back
вот тут есть волосня и сзади есть Воло
Well, I'm also from Ukraine Yes, damn Show me, there
Ну я тоже с Украины Да блин Покажи
really isn't, why isn't there
на реально нету да чего нету
hair on the back Well, so what now, not
волосний на спине Ну и что тепер не не
just Ira, I have a little bit, I wonder if
просто Ире у меня немножко есть мне
others had the same thing, not me, I
интересно или у других также было не я Я
just don't start, let's
те только не начинай давай вот э
talk about it there And there  tosi bosi there and so
говорить там А там тоси боси там и так
on everything is so
далее там всё так
I am an ordinary person they got tired of it I understand
по Я обычный человек запарили понял
Where are you from Krasnodar I
Ты откуда сам Краснодар Я же
told you I am from Rostov myself but I have been living in
сказал Я сам из Ростова родом Но живу в
California for 18
Калифорнии 18
years you did it again Come on I  I did the same thing
лет ты снова так сделал Давай я тоже так
Pony Oh my God, I didn't
сдела Поня Господи ну я
do anything to make it so that it wouldn't be like
же ничего сдела чтобы оно Тода не было
that Then it's not a question of tying it
этой во не вопрос завязать
up Everything's
у всё
fine yeah yeah What do you do as a hairdresser Yes, a
ладно да да Кем работаешь парикмахер Да
hairdresser And you can't cut your own hair
парикмахер Да и не можешь себе
stupid question What does the head have to do with it
постричь тупой вопрос Причём тут голова
and this And I thought you were only a head
и вот это А я думал ты только головной
hairdresser let's talk like this Okay,
парикмахер давай так говорить Ладно
good hairdresser Who is the
хоро парикмахер Кто такой
person who makes wigs and
человек тот который делает парики и
terry cloth correctly How do I feel about breasts
махры правильно Каким я отношусь к груди
Well, maybe it's a breast wig A wig is not Well,
Ну может это парик грудной Парик не Ну
wait, you asked me the question yourself I'm
подожди ты сам мне задал вопрос я тебе
answering you I don't want to swear there in no
отвечаю я не хочу ругаться там ни в коем
way well you  the hairdresser himself is right
случае ну ты сам парикмахер правильно
wait I told you that I am a
подожди я тебе сказал то что я
hairdresser here don't look
парикмахер вот здесь не смотри
hairdresser in German a wig is
парикмахер это ж по-немецки парик это
the hair on the head and ma is the hair on the body
волосы на голове а ма это волосы на теле
you want to tell me what
ты хочешь мне рассказать то что такое
pama is I know and in German I know what it is
пама я знаю и по-немецки я знаю что это
that's right I know that there is a haircut
так и есть я знаю что стрижка есть
Gunther there is an undercut there are these German
Гюнтер есть андеркат есть это немецкие
haircuts next what can you tell me so
стрижки дальше что ты мне расскажешь так
and here is a haircut What is it called I
а тут стрижка Как называется
don't have I have never had my chest cut and Gul has a
не имею Я груд не стриг никогда а Гюль
haircut  what are you doing Gul No I don't know
стрижку делаешь Какую Гюль Нет я не знаю
what it is in the Gul area when they cut someone's hair
что это в районе Гюль когда стригут кого
in the
в районе
Gul area I don't know what it is I won't lie I do
Гюль Я не знаю что это я Врать не буду я
n't know I can cut hair like the
не знаю я могу подстригать как вот
men come to me they tell me they'll do a
мужики приезжают мне говорят сделает там
haircut like this A got it got it all you
такую стриж А понял понял всё всё Ты
men  you cut I understood well no
мужиков стрижешь я понял ну нет потому
because I everything everything everything I understand Yes you
что я всё всё всё я Поня понял Да ты
cut men's hair understood everything No not
стрижёшь мужиков всё понял Нет не потому
because I well wait no not what are you telling
что я ну подожди не не что ты рассказать
me Look when I go to the men's room there
Смотри я когда хожу в мужской зал Там
women cut their hair in the men's room women
женщины стригут в мужском зале женщины
cut their hair and there well  I just exist And there is
стригут и там ну я просто есть А есть
one guy who gets his hair cut, these guys go to him
один мужик который стригут к нему ходят
to get their hair cut I
как раз вот эти чтобы их мужик постриг я
understood everything well you are
понял всё ну ты
this guy who is a men's
этот кто мужской
hairdresser you think
парикмахер тебе кажется
I am the best men's hairdresser because well
я самый лучший мужской парикмахер потому
in quotes because I always
что ну в кавычках потому что я всегда
talk to people and always  like, well, a
пообщаюсь с людьми и всегда как бы ну
male hairdresser is just a regular Well, you, you,
мужской просто парикмахер обыч Ну ты ты
during a haircut You touch and
во время стрижки Ты же трогаешь
receive from the client Yes, only the head
получаешь со клиента Да только голову Да
Well, you turn your head there like that, your neck
ну ты так голову там поверните так шею
Yes, yes, I don't  touching the neck neck there
Да да я не трогаю шею ше шея там
bend over Oh well that's enough Well yes yes yes
наклоните Ой ну хорош Ну да да да
relatively yes
относительно да
I only touch what is needed during a
я трогаю только то что нужно во время
haircut marine of course
подстрижки морской само собой
undercut
андеркат
Gunter let's say What haircuts are there now well
Гюнтер допустим Какие стрижки сейчас ну
what
то
I cut people Lord well damn
что я подстригаю людей Господи ну блин
stop it
брось ты
Well my wife and so on Farther
Ну у жена и так Дале
zare No I shadow lie
заре Нет я тене ври
there
туда
here when a man comes with unwashed
здесь когда мужчина приходит с немытой
hair you wash his hair No you with
головой ты моешь ему голову Нет ты с
dirty hair him Well I live in the village
грязной головой ему Ну я в деревне живу
I tell you caressing stand
Я же тебе говорю лаская стани
village
деревенский
hairdresser in short I understood this is such No well what's the point
парикмахер короче понял это такое Не ну
why Yes people are different people have different
смыс зачем Да люди разные у людей разная
work Well, let's say he's working
работа Ну смотри допустим если он пахат
there or Well, what is he doing there How do I
там или Ну что он там делает Откуда же я
know Well, how are people all different,
знаю Ну как люди все разные на
really You don't need to
правда Ты там не надо вот это
promote this there Well, people are all different,
пропагандировать там ну люди все разные
really And what kind of flags do you have on your
на самом деле А что у тебя за флаги на
T-shirt Yes,  I don't even have an American
майке Да у меня даже американский есть
flag here because I What kind of flags are these Yes
флаг здесь нету пото я Что за флаги Да я
I ordered from America on my T-shirt
в Я заказывал с Америки на ма на майке
What kind of
Что за
flags are these Yes this is South Park m Yes this is
флаги есть да это Южный парк м да это
South
Южный
Park flags  what countries Yes
парк флаги каких стран Да никаких это
none at all this is South Park What is
вообще никаких это Южный парк Что такое
South Park
Южный парк
cartoon really got it cartoon got it
мультик правда понял это мультик понял
South Well sapak or whatever it is
Южный Ну сапак или как там
here no walls
здесь ни стен там
there back and forth What are you laughing at
туда-сюда Да что ты угораешь запарил
really How old are you I'm 33 you
правда Сколько тебе лет мне 33 года ты
pulled out your hair again  Well, I apologize
снова воло сню вытянул Ну изде извиняюсь
Well,
Ну
damn, you just relaxed And what are you, you
блин ты просто расслабился А что ты это
are 33 years old and you are wearing a cartoon on yourself, a
те 33 года а ты мультик на себе носишь
cartoon, so it is,
мультик так он же
and you are 33 years old, why would you
так а тебе же 33 года зачем ты это
say that, this cartoon, so I have been watching it since I was
скажешь этот мульти так я его смотрю с
20, he is already 15 years old, a cartoon, you  since you're 20
20 лет уже ему 15 лет Мульти ты с 20 лет
you watch cartoons yes 13 years old you watch
смотришь мультик да 13 лет смотришь
cartoons so it's provocative it's
мультик так он провокационный же ж это
like dolls there or whatever you call it it's
как куклы Там или как назвать его это
like Yes at least watch one episode
как Да хоть одну серию посмотреть
you'll understand it's not scary scary not that you know
поймёшь не страшно страшно не это знаешь
how it is
как
well well it's a cartoon there in
это ну ну это мультик там
short such
короче такой
well how to
ну как
explain in short  a specific cartoon
объяснить Короче специфический мультик
there Barbara Rezen there some Kato
там Барбара резен там какой-то там Като
Well in short with their
Ну короче со своими
jokes these are cartoons like Griffins
приколами это мультики какти Грифины
I watched No I didn't watch The Simpsons
смотрел Нет не смотрел Симпсоны
no something like that but  you see I can't I
нет типа того но видишь я не могу я Томи
watched Tommy Jerry as a child Well, no, no,
Джерри смотрел в детстве Ну по не нуже
no, and then when I got older I did
не то а потом когда стал постарше Я уже
n't watch cartoons anymore No, the
не мультики смотрел нене же хороши
cartoons are good And this is, well, how are these those same
мультик А это ну как это это те самые
stupid cartoons with which Well, how are they, well,
дурацкие мультики с который Ну как там
in short, how are they  explain I can't
ну короче ну как их объяснить Я не могу
explain These are stupid cartoons in short
объяснить Это дебильные мультики короче
Why do you watch stupid
Зачем ты смотришь дебильные
cartoons you see it started
мультики знатно видишь оно началось е
when In ninety something year and Che
когда В девяносто каком-то году и Че
something relaxed no emotions
чтото расслабоне никаких там эмоций
nothing Just watch Watch you know
ничего Просто смотришь Смотришь зна го
well how this one like we have the series
ну как этот самой как у нас есть сериал
Kitchen there  well, like there's chaos there, there's a
Кухня там ну типа там беспредел там
series I haven't even heard of such
сериал Я не слышал Даже про такие
series that Well, you have different ones, we have
сериалы что Ну у вас-то другие у нас
different ones, well, in short, like some kind of, well, like a series, um,
другие ну короче типа как какой-то вот
like it's prime time or whatever it's
э как он прайм тайм или как он там
called, in short, some kind of series
называется Короче какой-нибудь э сериал
which is something like that well he's kind of walking they
который типа того ну он как бы идёт его
took him down yesterday he walked by there and they kind of forgot about him
сняли вчера там он прошёл и как бы с ним
Well it seems like until you started
забыли Ну ты походу пока ты не начал
explaining I at least understood a little bit how you
объяснять я хоть немножко понимал ты как
started to confuse your gift
начал у тебя дар
Yes  no well damn it's simpler well
запутать Да нет ну блин всё проще ну
how how can you explain the essence of
как как объяснить можешь объяснить суть
at least one episode of this cartoon
хотя бы одной серии этого мультика
which one exactly well this one of yours I don't
какого именно ну вот этого твоего Я не
know what it's called the one of
знаю как он называется Вот который у
yours South Park probably yes Well the
тебя Южного парка наверное да Ну
last one, for example, was about covid Well about
Последний допустим был про ковид Ну про
coronavirus such nonsense well  in fact,
коронавирус такой бред ну в натуре
the series was stupid. The last one was
дебильный серия была Вот последняя
really stupid, like, one
вообще дебильная типа то что один
of them turns out to be four.
из получается там четыре Ну главного
Well, the main character is right here. Well, even
героя получается вот здесь вот Ну даже
on the T-shirt, let's say. Take the
на майке вот допустим Взять снова
hair here again, and
волосня здесь н
what's his second name?
как его второго-то
Okay, it doesn't matter, four people, the
зовут Ладно неважно четыре человека
main character, in short.  one of you
главный герой по сути короче один из ты
again womb show how you again
снова лон показываешь как ты снова воло
hair show snyu Yes I'm sick of it Lord come on
сню показываешь Да задолбал Господи нука
I'll show you these Well
Я те покажу эти Ну
as you
как
can see
видно
here
вот
stn
стн
Kyle Cartman I
Кайл Картман
don't remember I won't lie I don't remember the last one's
не помню Врать не буду последнего не
name Kenny remembered
зовут Кени вспомнил
ke this cartoon
ке этому мультику
25 the point in the World Cup it doesn't matter fundamentally to
25 смысл в ЧМ это неважно принципиально
you  you need to remember their names or
тебе нужно вспомнить как их зовут или
something or tell them the episode What exactly Well
что или расказать серию Что именно Ну
tell me some episode a smart episode a
расскажи какую-то серию умную серию
smart episode there aren't any you watch idiotic episodes
умную серию их нет ты дебильные серии
all idiotic episodes So you're
смотришь все дебильные серии Так ты же
standing there standing  stupid because of this yes I'm not
стоишь стоишь тупым от этого да я не
saying that they are smart I just
говорю то что они умные Я просто их
watch them not because they are idiotic or
смотрю не потому что они дебильные или
not because they are smart but because
не не потому что они умные а потому что
well you always s everything that it is
ну ты всегда сь всё что оно у
tie your hair back purely out of respect
волосы завяжи сзади чисто изза уважения
I will do
я сделаю
well Well and the films  what smok
хорошо Ну а фильмы какие смо
ka exactly What films do
ка именно Какие фильмы
you watch very different 8th parallel Front line
смотришь очень разные 8 параллель Линия
[music]
[музыка]
raid what was it called
рейд как он назывался три раза
re-shoot three times when was the First World War
переснимать когда Первая война Мировая
what was it not the
была как он не
world I don't remember forgot the
мировая не помню забыл
name something long there very
название что-то там длинное очень
E what
Э что
else well nothing provocative nothing
ещё ну никаких провокационных ничего не
I watch I'm an ordinary person I watch
смотрю Я обычный человек я смотрю Один
Home Alone when it's New
дома когда Новый
Year's all these things every New
год всё таких каких-то там каждый новый
Year you watch Home Alone
год смотришь Один дома
No well it happens sometimes but not now I
Да нет ну бывает когда но сейчас нет
used to watch I understood And who do you
уже Раньше смотрел понял А как ты
think Crimea is Crimea You know
считаешь чей Крым Крым Ты же знаешь
the Crimeans and it's in cartoons  so did you
крымчан а это в мультиках так этих ты
recognize these or how No I just know that the
узнал или как Нет я просто знаю что
Crimeans as the Crimeans I will say so and it will be
крымчан как крымчане скажу так и будет
so it is necessary for it to come out from there so that
так надо чтоб оттуда вышла чтобы
the Crimeans would say something
крымчане что-то сказали
Here you offend me and I offend For  what For that
Вот ты обижаешь меня да обижаю За что За
why didn't I tell you I'm
что почему я же тебе не говорил Я тебе
telling you so you don't recognize Crimea as
говорю так ты не признаешь Крым
Ukraine And damn why don't I recognize I didn't
Украиной А блин почему я не признаю я не
say anything then tell me Crimea is
говорил ничего тогда скажи Крым - это
Ukraine
Украина
Ukraine is always a separate state
Украина всегда отдельным государством
This is so tell me that Crimea is part of
Это са так скажи что Крым - это часть
Ukraine I  I don't know tell me Crimea is
Украины Я не знаю скажи это Крым - это
part of
часть
Ukraine I don't know
Украины Я не знаю
tell me I can't say Well I didn't
скажи я не могу сказать Ну я же там не
live there Well how about that Well Irkutsk Irkutsk
жил Ну как А хорошо а Иркутска Иркутская
region is part of
область - это часть
Russia Well yes You lived there no So
России Ну да А ты там жил нет Так
wait What about Crimea you can't say  say
подожди А что про Крым не можешь сказать
you didn't live about the Irkutsk region can you
ты не жила про иркутскую область можешь
yes I about the circle Lord about
да я про кру Господи про
Irkutsk Oh come on I can't even say well let's
иркутс Ой да ладно не могу сказать даже
say I want you know how to be
ну скажем так я хочу знаешь как вот если
honest for me from the fact that it became Russia
честно мне от того что он стал Россией
nothing good and for my
ни не стало хорошего и для моих
relatives let's say exactly the same  if it's not
родственников допустим точно так же не
good then maybe it's better to give it
стало хорошего то может лучше отдать его
back to Ukraine and not in the minds well then you
назад Украине и не умах ну так вы
ask who not me You are a hairdresser of
спросите у кого не у меня Ты парикмахер
Ladoga village so here's a hairdresser I
Ладожской стани так вот парикмахер Я
know what I'll
тебе знаеш что
tell you well to hell I'll show you better hair
скажу ну нафиг я лучше волоса покажу
even for free souls
даже бесплатно души
still hair something again  pull up Well,
ещ волосами что-то снова подтяни Ну
after all, I even gave you wine, dezhi, that's it,
всё-таки я тебе даже вино дежи вот так
and that's it A And I don't know about that Well,
вот и всё А А насчёт этого я знать не
who am I And what do you think
знаю Ну кто я такой А как считаешь
Why did the war between Ukraine and Russia start,
Почему война Украины и России началась
why did he start, hold on, hold on, his hand will fall
почему он нача держи держи руку упадёт
Yes, why on Well, okay, I
Да почему на Ну ладно
'll do it again  time Why did the war between
сделаю ещё раз Почему началась война
Ukraine and
Украины и
Russia start Why did it start
России Почему началась
Yes Lyoshka for the resource Probably who is
Да Лёшка за ресурс Наверно кто
to blame Who is to
виноват Кто
blame yes How do I know you see The thing is
виноват да Я ж откуда знаю видишь Дело в
that I can't even answer I don't
том что я даже не могу ответить Я не
know The thing is that say there let's say
знаю Дело в том что сказать там допустим
someone yes who is to blame I  I don't
кто-то да кто виноват я не
know I'm so innocent about it That's why
знаю Я настолько невен в этом Потому
I didn't participate in it at all I only know what I know BN The
участвовал я единственно зна что знаю БН
only thing I know is that my
Я единственное что знаю то что мои вот
well close brothers are dying there and that's it
ну братья близкие там погибают и всё А
Why are they dying Who is to blame for
почему они погибают кто виноват в том
them dying Yes, he knows what's
что они погибают Да его знает что
going on  Well, who is to blame for your
происходит Ну кто виноват в том что Твои
brothers dying I don't know Well, what do you
братья погибают Я не знаю Ну как ты
think I
думаешь я как
think Well,
думаю конно
who is to
кто
blame at the moment
виноват в данный момент
Yes, he knows I can't
да знает я не могу
say Let's do it Who
сказать давай так кто на кого
attacked whom You see, you start to
напал напал ть видишь ты начинаешь эту
say this Well,
говорить Ну
okay Well, maybe Russia naturally
ладно Ну возможно Россия естественно
Most likely Russia attacked yes  Yes, she attacked in the
всего Россия напала да Да она напала не
wrong way, I mean, how did she attack? Yes, I
так она в смысле как она-то напала Да
understand.
понятно
Well, that's all there.
Ну там же это всё
Well, okay. Well, look, if Russia
это Ну хорошо Ну смотри если Россия
attacked Ukraine, then who's
напала на Украину то кто
to blame. Now we're again coming to
виноват Мы сейчас опять приходим к
practical questions, the same ones,
дельным вопросам одним и тем же ну
seriously, the
серьёзно
same ones. Well,  Well, let's talk about the same
одно и тоже Ну ну давай будем об одном и
thing Well,
том же Ну на самом
actually Maybe it's easier to talk about the fact that I'm a
деле Может проще поговорить о том что я
hairdresser and you do something else
парикмахер а ты чем-то другим
Yes You're a hairdresser I do
занимаешься да Ты парикмахер Я занимаюсь
something else Tell me, a hairdresser,
чем-то другим Скажи мне парикмахер
a man who does something else,
мужику который занимается чем-то другим
who is to blame for that  that Russia attacked
кто виноват в том что Россия напала на
Ukraine How do I know who I am I
Украину Да я откуда знаю я кто это я те
can cut your hair I told you Come I'll
могу подстрич я те сказал Приезжай я те
cut your hair everything
подстригу всё
Let's go to the
Съездим на
sea How do I
море откуда ж я
know Well it's true they invited you to the sea
знаю Ну правда на море ещ
Mori Well
приглашали Мори Ну
okay go to Krasnodar to some village
окей ехать в Краснодар в какое-то село
so that you  there a guy cut his hair and went with
чтобы тебя там мужик постриг и поехал с
you to the sea This is of course still Family
тобой на море Это конечно то ещ Семейные
values Yes Okay you want to wait you have
ценности Да О'кей ты хочешь подожди ты
already insulted me three times why did you do this to the village
уже три раза меня оскорбил за что село
of Ladoga
ладожскую
And why can't you decide
сделал А зачем ты не можешь определиться
Why not A  why did you insult me now
Почему не А зачем ты меня сейчас
I didn't say anything like that to you
оскорбил я тебе ни такого не говорил
because you don't respect
потому что ты не уважаешь
Ukrainians stop
украинцев стоп
Yes I'm not scared Lord I don't
Да я не ужа Господи я не уважаю
respect Ukrainians you don't respect
украинцев не уважаешь
Ukrainians at least I said a word
украинцев хоть слово я сказал
you didn't say anything good And at least I said something bad I
ты не сказал хорошего А я хоть плохого
said something bad you said you don't
сказал сказал какое ты сказал что не
know  who attacked Ukraine and who is
знаешь кто напал на Украину и кто
to blame And this is an insult This is
виноват А это оскорбление Это
an insult Well, you see, for you, this is
оскорбление Да ну видишь для тебя это
an insult Yes, for every Ukrainian This is
оскорбление да для каждого украинца Это
an insult Well, please forgive me I
оскорбление Ну извини меня пожалуйста Я
didn't do it You did it You Apologize
так не сделал ты сделал Ты Извинись
to me as a Ukrainian I
передо мной как перед украинцем я те
told you I apologize, you apologize Ukrainians
сказал извиняюсь те извинись Украин
should  who am I talking to you as?
должен ть кем я только с тобой общаюсь
No, wait, you insulted all Ukrainians in my face,
Не ну подожди ты в моём лице оскорбил
I'm telling you again. I
украинцев я тебе ещё раз повторяю Я
apologize to you. Maybe I
извиняюсь перед тобой Возможно я что-то
showed something somehow wrong. Okay, I understand. I
проявил как-то не так Ладно понял Я
accept and convey your apology to all Ukrainians.
принимаю передаю всем украинцам твоё
Now look who I am.  again I did
извинение теперь смотри кто я опять же я
not insult all Ukra wine who is to blame
не оскорблял всех Укра вино кто виноват
for Putin attacking Ukraine
в том что Путин напал на Украину
Well let's see if there is Putin there is
Ну давай смотри если есть Путин есть
Ukraine Putin attacks Ukraine  Who is
Украина Путин нападает на Украину Кто
to blame, there is Zelensky, there is Putin, and what
виноват есть Зеленский есть Путин и что
next? Yes, but it was not Zelensky who attacked, but Putin who
дальше Да но не Зеленский напал а Путин
attacked, so who is
напал то кто
to blame? And you are not confused by one thing, that
виноват а тебя не смущает один момент то
suddenly one person appeared who
что вдруг появился один человек который
was nobody in Donbass, and then he
на Донбассе был никто а потом он
appeared, and suddenly now he decided to
появился и вдруг теперь он решил
sign a peace treaty with  Putin to you
подписать мирный договор с Путиным тебе
this is generally who is to blame for the fact that
это вообще вону кто виноват в том что
Putin attacked Ukraine
Путин напал на Украину
Yes, how should I
Да я откуда
know again look Putin attacked really And
знаю ещ раз смотри Путин напал правда А
you listen to me here when there was DPR LPR
ты меня Послушай сюда когда был ДНР лнр
now a new one has appeared they have this same one
сейчас появился новый у них этот самый
how is he there well listen for 2 seconds
как он там ну послушай 2 секунды прежде
before waving  head
чем махать головой
Listen if you don't want to listen I'm listening to
Послушай не хочешь да слушать я слушаю
you come on
тебя давай
When the new one appeared now DPR
Когда появился новый сейчас ДНР
LPR this same what is it called Lord
лнр этот самый как он называется Господи
MR
МР
there and somehow decided to make peace with
там и каким-то решил помириться с
Putin
Путиным
what who is to blame for Putin attacking
какого кто виноват в том что Путин напал
Ukraine can you tell me the name sister name
на Украину можешь сказать имя сестра имя
Yes where am I from  I know I held a candle
Да я откуда знаю я свечку держал
for you again you have a dream Well come on tell me
у тебя снова у тебя сно Ну давай скажи
who is who is to blame who is
кто кто тин виноват кто
Putin seriously Yes one person well he
Путин серьёзно Да один человек ну он
took and attacked Ukraine And
взял напал на Украину А
who I just told you  I'm telling you something else,
кто Я тебе только что рассказываю другое
you listen, you start
ты слушаешь ты начинаешь фейс пами
throwing faces at me, I'm telling you that the person
кидаться я тебе говорю то что человек
who is now in power in
который сейчас у власти в
the DPR, how did he
ДНР как он там
get there? Did you elect him? No,
появился его вы его выбирали Нет его
Russia put him there. Putin asked the question
поставила Россия Путин поставил вопрос
again. And you're yelling at me, why did you send me,
ещё раз А ты на меня орёшь за что е
excuse the expression. Listen.  I
посил извиняю выражение Послушай меня
was listening, I wasn't listening correctly And you listen
слушал не слушал правильно А ты послушай
This is what watching these
Вот к чему приводят смотрение вот этих
southern ones leads to You listen to this
южных Ты послушай кам Вот это
Who is to blame Just tell me the culprit
Кто виноват Назови мне виновного просто
Tell me
Назови
the culprit of what When in the fact that Russia
виновного в чём Когда в том что Россия
attacked
напала на
Ukraine I don't
Украину Я не
know Putin didn't attack but I don't know who is to blame
знаю не напал Путин а виноват я не
and who made Putin attack I
знаю а кто заставил Путина напасть
can't say Come on if your neighbor attacked you
не могу сказать Давай если на тебя напал
Who is
сосед Кто
to blame neighbor so if Putin attacked
виноват сосед так если Путин напал на
Ukraine Who is
Украину Кто
to blame a small nuance a small
виноват нюанс маленький маленький
nuance I'm fed up Well me Irika
нюанс жа запарил Ну ме Ирика
already you don't understand
уже тыж не понимаешь
with Kato let's say here Novorossiya
с Като вот допустим вот новороссия
Malorossiya suddenly some appeared there  then
малороссия вдруг появились там какие-то
unexpected these same ones look again
неожиданные эти самые ещё раз смотри
if a neighbor attacked you the neighbor is to blame
если на тебя напал сосед виноват сосед
So you can listen to me just
Так ты меня можешь послушать просто
call just  Name who is to blame Name
назви просто Назови Кто виноват Назови
this
этого
someone you are listening to I hear but you do
кого-то ты слушаешь походу я слышу но ты
not name the culprit specifically the
не называешь виновного конкретно
culprit I will now bring you to this
виновного я те сейчас приведу к этому
naturally it will be Putin you
естественно это будет Путин те спокойно
will be calm like this Name it Say who is to blame So I
будет так Назови Скажи что виноват Так я
want to explain to you why this is all
тебе объяснить хочу почему это Это вся
Name it Who is to blame  And
Назови Кто виноват И
that's all, who is to blame,
всё что ли кто виноват
who is to blame for
ты кто виноват в
what, that you don't have basic
чём в том что у тебя нету элементарного
cognitive abilities, cognitive
когнитивных способность когнитивный
dissonance, etc. What are you talking about? In the
диссонанс и прочее Что ты гонишь В
sense that I am to blame,
смысле что я виноват
I will always answer your question, but
я тебе отвечу всегда на твой вопрос но
only one thing. I can't understand what
только единственное Я не могу понять что
exactly you are asking.  who exactly is to blame
ты именно спрашиваешь кто именно виноват
for
в
the war know who is to blame for the war I don't
войне знать кто виноват в войне я не
know who is to blame Why Because I
знаю кто виноват Почему Потому что не
can't answer you this
могу ответить тебе на этот
question
вопрос
Well don't freak out Calm down I'll tell you So
Ну не психуй Успокойся я скажу Так
wait I'm I'm I've heard the opinion before
подожди я я я ра Я раньше слышал мнение
that these cartoons need to be banned
что нужно запрещать вот эти мультфильмы
in society there  The Simpsons South Park And so
в обществе там Симпсоны Южный парк И так
on I laughed at this that there is no need to
дальше я смеялся с этого что не нужно
ban you what And now I have an
запрещать вы что А сейчас у меня
epiphany of whom cartoons yes this is
Прозрение кого мультики да это
stupidity it seems to me that when people
глупость мне кажется что люди когда
watch such cartoons they become stupid And
смотрят такие мультфильмы они тупеют А
degrade
деградируют
yes  It seems to you that
да Тебе кажется
I see the result in front of me Well, come on,
я вижу перед собой результат Ну брось ты
let's throw nastiness Well,
Ну давай давай гадость кидаться Ну
seriously You're just asking
серьёзно Ты просто спрашиваешь
as a rhetorical question and what do you want from me
как риторический вопрос и что ты от меня
Your hair is falling out again It's
хочеш у тебя снова волосы вылазят это
aesthetically unpleasant Well,
эстетически неприятно Ну
close it Okay, out of respect I
закрой Ладно из уважения
'll do it no matter what the opponents are  There
сделаю как бы там не было противники Там
and so on I respect I do
и так далее Я уважаю
n't care what you think about
пофиг что думаешь про
America A wonderful
Америку Прекрасная
country now when Trump comes he will
страна сейчас когда Трамп придёт он
finally lower the price of this itself no
наконец-таки понизит цену на это само
Yes accordingly a little Well
неть Да соответственно прит чуть-чуть Ну
somehow it will adapt most likely
как-нибудь адаптируется скорее всего
considering that I hope that the
э учитывая то что я надеюсь что откроют
borders will finally open  -so I can buy
границы наконец-таки я могу смогу купить
some
кроссовки какие-нибудь
Adidas sneakers and so on and so forth and Well or
адидасовские Там и так далее и Ну или
Nike and everything for the average
найковский и как бы всё для обычного
person damn I hope so that the
обывателя блин Надеюсь так то что открыт
borders are open we will be able to order goods and
границы мы сможем заказывать товары и
everything is so
всё столько
globally good I'll run further I
глобально хорошо Побегу я дальше я
hope that it will be like this
надеюсь что так
Okay people don't watch these
О'кей народ не смотрите эти
cartoons Maybe it's
мультики Вдруг это
contagious like squeak comment subscribe to
заразно лайк писка комент подпишись на
my Telegram live  now axis win and
мий Telegram прям зараз ось вин а
Popik this is very and very important YouTube
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
is busy with us through scarg ORV your ban and very
заня нас через скарг ОРВ твый бан и дуже
many videos I don't show to people at times I don't
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams That's
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
why we Mali operational links pp
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок ппи
right now and while there in telegram okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
video more  also interesting and useful information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we will oblige you with the trim fast
и мы повинни вами трима постный
operational links
оперативный звязок
independently in that che will show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube Слава Украине подпишись